<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Improv Raleigh Events</title>
    <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/calendar/</link>
    <description>Comedy shows and events at Improv Raleigh</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 22:15:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Isaa Truuue Tour with Michael Yo (Jan 2-4)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/isaa+truuue+tour+with+michael+yo/14713273/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/isaa+truuue+tour+with+michael+yo/14713273/</guid>
      <description>Jan 2-4 - A 2-time Emmy nominee, regular on the Joe Rogan Experience, host of the Michael Yo Show and fresh off his critically acclaimed comedy special Blasian, Michael Yo is a comedian/actor/host keeping busy in all of Hollywood’s platforms. Now, Michael is a proud father and loving husband with a bottomless pool of material about his family. Right after having his son and a viral appearance showcasing his talents to the world on America’s Got Talent, Michael Yo brings his all new We’re StillHere2020 Tour to your city. In stand up, Michael came up under the wings of Chelsea Handler and Jo Koy and now headlines all over the country. As an actor, Michael recently reoccurred on “Kevin Can Wait,” shot a Damon Wayan Jr.’s pilot “Happy Together” for CBS and was a principal in Facebook’s upcoming Facebook Watch first sitcom series, “Starter Pack.” Michael was previously seen covering celebrity news on “The Insider,” “Extra,” “E! News,” as well as guest co-hosting CBS’ “The Talk.” Michael continues to appear as a hot topics guest on “The Wendy Williams Show.” The self-proclaimed “Half-Black Brother with a Korean Mother” was born and raised in Houston and now lives in Los Angeles with his family.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/13/32/76/43_Original.jpg?v=5" alt="Isaa Truuue Tour with Michael Yo"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:15:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Johnson in 3D (Apr 3-4)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/josh+johnson+in+3d/14702953/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/josh+johnson+in+3d/14702953/</guid>
      <description>Apr 3-4 - With over 7 million followers across his social media, Josh Johnson was recently called “the funniest guy on the internet” by WIRED and is a star on the rise. He is an Emmy-nominated writer, stand-up comedian, actor, and NAACP award-winner from Louisiana by way of Chicago. Johnson is currently a rotating host and correspondent on Comedy Central’s Emmy &amp; Peabody Award-winning program The Daily Show where he was previously a writer for seven years. Johnson is also a former writer and performer on NBC’s The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon, where he made his late-night debut in 2017. As a stand-up, Johnson headlines theaters, clubs, colleges, and festivals around the world and you can currently find him on his FLOWERS TOUR. He is also a prolific writer and performer who puts out weekly stand-up sets on his YouTube channel. In 2024, Johnson released 28 hours of stand up and he is on track to exceed that amount this year. The content on his YouTube channel has been viewed over 340 million times by people all over the world.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/13/33/28/13_Original.jpg?v=1" alt="Josh Johnson in 3D"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:15:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mojo Brookzz: I Know You F*ckin Lying Tour (Jan 15-18)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/mojo+brookzz%3a+i+know+you+f%2ackin+lying+tour/13996124/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/mojo+brookzz%3a+i+know+you+f%2ackin+lying+tour/13996124/</guid>
      <description>Jan 15-18 - Dyon “Mojo” Brooks is an actor, writer, producer, and stand-up comedian. As a comic, Brooks is nationally acclaimed and celebrated having toured with legends such as Mike Epps, Martin Lawrence, and Deon Cole to name a few. He recently wrapped his headlining nationwide “Unhand Me Now” Tour which sold out every single with multiple added shows in nearly every location. This tour also marks Brooks’ transition from fully sold-out club weekends into headlining theatres with sold out stops at Atlanta’s Center Stage, Memphis’s Minglewood Hall, and two sold-out Sunday night shows at Chicago’s historic Vic theatre. Additionally, Dyon can be seen on the most recent Season [21] of Nick Cannon’s WILD N OUT, having been hand selected by Cannon who is a fan of Brooks viral sketch comedy videos that can be found across his social media pages, which have amassed millions of views and over 26.5 million likes. Brooks counts more than 1.1 million Instagram followers, 1.5 million Facebook followers, and over 1.3 million TikTok followers. A Chicago native, Brooks frequently collaborates with the Chicago Bears and contributed to a mid-west Emmy win for his writing efforts across commercial and digital work the team continues to do with him. Additionally, Brooks has lent his comedic acting talents to music videos including Lil Durk’s hit Sad Songs. When not entertaining audiences, Brooks gives back to his community in Chicago, dedicating his time and resources to support youth development programs, demonstrating his commitment to making a positive impact beyond the stage and screen. From February to May of 2025, Brooks will again join the multi-city WE THEM ONES arena tour – a package which he was a part of from its inception in 2024. The Mike Epps hosted tour features acts such as Karlous Miller, Tony Roberts, and Kountry Wayne with Brooks in a prominent position within the line up. Following the conclusion of WE THEM ONES, Brooks will set out on his fourth headlining tour with stops at multiple different theatres across the nation. Plans on screen for 2025 include going out with a few different original ideas across film and television while continuing to expand his reach with auditions across both comedy and drama.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/12/74/70/24_Original.jpg?v=4" alt="Mojo Brookzz: I Know You F*ckin Lying Tour"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:15:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mix &amp; Mingle Tour 2025 starring Sheryl Underwood, Kyle Erby &amp; Mike Washington (Mar 20-21)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/the+mix+%26+mingle+tour+2025+starring+sheryl+underwood%2c+kyle+erby+%26+mike+washington/14353533/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/the+mix+%26+mingle+tour+2025+starring+sheryl+underwood%2c+kyle+erby+%26+mike+washington/14353533/</guid>
      <description>Mar 20-21 - Owner and CEO - Pack Rat Productions Inc. Entertainer Entrepreneur Philanthropist &amp; 23rd International President of Zeta Phi Beta Sorority Inc. Sheryl Underwood is a savvy businesswoman philanthropist and a multi-faceted multi-media entrepreneur who is recognized as one of the most articulate well-informed women of our time. She is a much sought after entertainer and public speaker who is described as one of the world’s brightest contemporary humorists. Underwood is Owner and Chief Executive Officer of Pack Rat Productions Inc. and is the 23rd International President of Zeta Phi Beta Sorority Inc. the only full-time entertainer to ever hold the sorority’s highest post. Underwood joined the television show THE TALK on CBS for the start of season two sitting alongside hosts Julie Chen Sara Gilbert Sharon Osbourne and Aisha Tyler. The show averages over 2 million viewers per day. With Underwood at the table THE TALK received its first Daytime Emmy nomination and a 5th year renewal on CBS television. Underwood who has received numerous awards and accolades was named one of the 10 most influential talk show hosts on Twitter in 2012. Underwood has appeared on multiple episodes of the Emmy winning CBS daytime drama The Young and the Restless and has starred in such films as Bullworth (starring Warren Beatty) I Got the Hook Up and Beauty Shop (starring Queen Latifah). In addition, Underwood was the host of Black Entertainment Television’s (BET’s) Comic View and Holla a talk show she created and produced which was loosely based on Bill Maher’s Politically Incorrect. She is a weekly contributor on the Steve Harvey Morning Show also serving as “guest host” and appears on The Steve Harvey Project the television version of the show airing on BET Centric. Underwood also hosted The Sheryl Underwood Show on Jamie Foxx’s The Foxxhole airing on Sirius 106/XM 149 where she provided a mix of political satire comedy and music. She can be heard on the radio daily from 3--?7 pm on “Sheryl Underwood Radio” airing on The Juice 107.3 (WJUC) in Toledo Ohio and North Carolina A&amp;T State University’s WNAA 90.1 FM. Underwood was the host of Martin Lawrence Presents 1st Amendment Stand-Up and is a former contributor to the Tom Joyner Morning Show. Underwood has appeared on the Dr. Phil Show FOX television network morning show Fox and Friends the Joy Behar Show WPIX in New York City The View created by ABC News Correspondent Barbara Walters OMG! Insider and CBS This Morning.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/12/99/78/63_Original.jpg?v=6" alt="The Mix &amp; Mingle Tour 2025 starring Sheryl Underwood, Kyle Erby &amp; Mike Washington"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 00:15:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mojo Brookzz: I Know You F*ckin Lying Tour (Jan 15-18)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/mojo+brookzz%3a+i+know+you+f%2ackin+lying+tour/13904924/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/mojo+brookzz%3a+i+know+you+f%2ackin+lying+tour/13904924/</guid>
      <description>Jan 15-18 - Dyon “Mojo” Brooks is an actor, writer, producer, and stand-up comedian. As a comic, Brooks is nationally acclaimed and celebrated having toured with legends such as Mike Epps, Martin Lawrence, and Deon Cole to name a few. He recently wrapped his headlining nationwide “Unhand Me Now” Tour which sold out every single with multiple added shows in nearly every location. This tour also marks Brooks’ transition from fully sold-out club weekends into headlining theatres with sold out stops at Atlanta’s Center Stage, Memphis’s Minglewood Hall, and two sold-out Sunday night shows at Chicago’s historic Vic theatre. Additionally, Dyon can be seen on the most recent Season [21] of Nick Cannon’s WILD N OUT, having been hand selected by Cannon who is a fan of Brooks viral sketch comedy videos that can be found across his social media pages, which have amassed millions of views and over 26.5 million likes. Brooks counts more than 1.1 million Instagram followers, 1.5 million Facebook followers, and over 1.3 million TikTok followers. A Chicago native, Brooks frequently collaborates with the Chicago Bears and contributed to a mid-west Emmy win for his writing efforts across commercial and digital work the team continues to do with him. Additionally, Brooks has lent his comedic acting talents to music videos including Lil Durk’s hit Sad Songs. When not entertaining audiences, Brooks gives back to his community in Chicago, dedicating his time and resources to support youth development programs, demonstrating his commitment to making a positive impact beyond the stage and screen. From February to May of 2025, Brooks will again join the multi-city WE THEM ONES arena tour – a package which he was a part of from its inception in 2024. The Mike Epps hosted tour features acts such as Karlous Miller, Tony Roberts, and Kountry Wayne with Brooks in a prominent position within the line up. Following the conclusion of WE THEM ONES, Brooks will set out on his fourth headlining tour with stops at multiple different theatres across the nation. Plans on screen for 2025 include going out with a few different original ideas across film and television while continuing to expand his reach with auditions across both comedy and drama.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/12/74/64/74_Original.jpg?v=2" alt="Mojo Brookzz: I Know You F*ckin Lying Tour"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 00:15:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wicked Sing-Along Drag Brunch (Feb 1)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/wicked+sing-along+drag+brunch/14732063/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/wicked+sing-along+drag+brunch/14732063/</guid>
      <description>Feb 1 - Drag Brunch is the best thing you can do on a Sunday. Don't miss a fun fully immersive show with Flip Phone Events. Each show is totally different and unique with a captivating theme. Get ready to party and you'll have a good time. You'll see the top drag talent from around the country, and we promise you'll leave with a smile!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/13/34/59/13_Original.jpg?v=4" alt="Wicked Sing-Along Drag Brunch"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dov Davidoff (Dec 27-28)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/dov+davidoff/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/dov+davidoff/</guid>
      <description>Dec 27-28 - Dov Davidoff currently appears on HBO’s Crashing and NBC’s Shades of Blue with Jennifer Lopez and Ray Liotta. He’s been seen on The Tonight Show and Late Night with Jimmy Kimmel as well as a lead role alongside Mark Wahlberg in the Movie Invincible. He’s done a comedy special for Comedy Central and Showtime, and recently had a memoir published by St. Martin’s Press entitled ‘Road Dog’, life and reflections of a standup comic from the road.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/07/81/64/21/Original.jpg?v=1" alt="Dov Davidoff"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaa Truuue Tour with Michael Yo (Jan 2-4)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/isaa+truuue+tour+with+michael+yo/14713263/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/isaa+truuue+tour+with+michael+yo/14713263/</guid>
      <description>Jan 2-4 - A 2-time Emmy nominee, regular on the Joe Rogan Experience, host of the Michael Yo Show and fresh off his critically acclaimed comedy special Blasian, Michael Yo is a comedian/actor/host keeping busy in all of Hollywood’s platforms. Now, Michael is a proud father and loving husband with a bottomless pool of material about his family. Right after having his son and a viral appearance showcasing his talents to the world on America’s Got Talent, Michael Yo brings his all new We’re StillHere2020 Tour to your city. In stand up, Michael came up under the wings of Chelsea Handler and Jo Koy and now headlines all over the country. As an actor, Michael recently reoccurred on “Kevin Can Wait,” shot a Damon Wayan Jr.’s pilot “Happy Together” for CBS and was a principal in Facebook’s upcoming Facebook Watch first sitcom series, “Starter Pack.” Michael was previously seen covering celebrity news on “The Insider,” “Extra,” “E! News,” as well as guest co-hosting CBS’ “The Talk.” Michael continues to appear as a hot topics guest on “The Wendy Williams Show.” The self-proclaimed “Half-Black Brother with a Korean Mother” was born and raised in Houston and now lives in Los Angeles with his family.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/13/32/76/43_Original.jpg?v=5" alt="Isaa Truuue Tour with Michael Yo"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aries Spears (Mar 6-8)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/aries+spears/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/aries+spears/</guid>
      <description>Mar 6-8 - Ever since Chicago native Aries Spears was 14 years old he has been a force to be reckoned with in the comedy scene throughout America. His quick wit charisma and ferociously aggressive style of comedy have earned him critical acclaim high accolades and above all a busy schedule. From being a regular on Fox’s Mad TV starring in feature films appearing on a number of national talk shows and continually touring the country with his stand-up Aries’s talents are becoming recognized and appreciated throughout the entertainment industry. As a principal cast member on Fox’s hit sketch comedy show Mad TV Aries brought a fresh hip style to the already-edgy program from the third through the tenth season. The producers made full use of many of Aries’s talents by calling on him frequently to create new hilarious characters and write sketches. Some of the many recurring characters that Aries is famous for on the show include: Belma Buttons Bill Cosby Jesse Jackson Mike Tyson Walter (Crackheads) Reggie (Erascist) Dollar Bill Montgomery Shaquille O'Neal The Klumps Michael Jackson Sisqo Evander Holyfield El Diablo Negro and more. Aries also boasts a number of uproarious impersonations on the show that include James Brown Al Pacino and his childhood idol Eddie Murphy. The Aries-branded sketch “Talkin’ American” was Mad TV’s most popular bit keeping fans tuned in and boosting Mad’s ratings impressively on Saturday night. Aries has also found great success in the world of feature films. At the age of 17 after being spotted in a comedy club Aries landed a part in the movie Home of Angels which also starred Abe Vigoda and Sherman Helmsley but never saw a theatrical release. He then appeared in Out-of-Sync and portrayed Red Foxx in Warner Bros.’s Why Do Fools Fall In Love. In addition Aries starred alongside John Leguizamo in TriStar’s The Pest and delivered his most notable performance to date as Cuba Gooding Jr.’s brother in Columbia’s blockbuster hit Jerry Maguire. Aries was born on April 3 1975 in Chicago but grew up in New Jersey. He remembers at the young age of six being the funnyman of the household and impersonating family members at the dinner table during holidays. By age 14 Aries was belting out his fresh stylings in front of paying audiences at local clubs around his hometown. Shortly thereafter he appeared on Russell Simmons’s Def Comedy Jam on HBO and Showtime at the Apollo. The word was out about the prodigal superstar from then on and in 1992 Aries moved to Los Angeles. He quickly landed a recurring role on NBC’s A Different World and was signed to a huge development deal at one of the major television studios. The following year Aries found himself starring in the short-lived CBS series South of Sunset with former Eagles guitarist Glenn Frey. Although the series didn’t last long it did not discourage other networks from tapping Aries’s talents for their projects as he soon appeared in Crosstown Traffic and Brisco County Jr. for Fox. Ultimately Aries’s fierce momentum landed him on Mad TV as a series regular where he thrived for eight seasons. Aries continues to spread his comedic wings with the development of feature film projects which he is currently involved in writing. He is presently developing a feature project based on an original character that he created on Mad TV as well as a thriller about a young black man immersed in hip-hop culture. Additionally Aries has made appearances on many talk shows including: Loveline Vibe Keenen Ivory Wayans Soul Train and Late Friday. He has also lent his voice to an animated character on C-Bear and Jamal and had a recurring stint on Fox’s The Best Damn Sports Show Period where he created some of the show’s funniest characters during his short time there. Aries maintains a strong connection to his African roots and is involved in many charitable events including a number of organizations that help abused women. He feels blessed to have been able to achieve everything that he has but he in no way intends on stopping there. Given the extreme growing success rate of action comedies coming out of Hollywood it’s safe to say that Aries Spears will be in demand for quite some time.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/07/82/44/81/Original.jpg?v=1?v=2?v=3?v=4?v=5" alt="Aries Spears"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Johnson in 3D (Apr 3-4)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/josh+johnson+in+3d/14702923/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/josh+johnson+in+3d/14702923/</guid>
      <description>Apr 3-4 - With over 7 million followers across his social media, Josh Johnson was recently called “the funniest guy on the internet” by WIRED and is a star on the rise. He is an Emmy-nominated writer, stand-up comedian, actor, and NAACP award-winner from Louisiana by way of Chicago. Johnson is currently a rotating host and correspondent on Comedy Central’s Emmy &amp; Peabody Award-winning program The Daily Show where he was previously a writer for seven years. Johnson is also a former writer and performer on NBC’s The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon, where he made his late-night debut in 2017. As a stand-up, Johnson headlines theaters, clubs, colleges, and festivals around the world and you can currently find him on his FLOWERS TOUR. He is also a prolific writer and performer who puts out weekly stand-up sets on his YouTube channel. In 2024, Johnson released 28 hours of stand up and he is on track to exceed that amount this year. The content on his YouTube channel has been viewed over 340 million times by people all over the world.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/13/31/95/03_Original.jpg?v=6" alt="Josh Johnson in 3D"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kountry Wayne (Feb 20-22)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/kountry+wayne/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/kountry+wayne/</guid>
      <description>Feb 20-22 - Wayne Colley, better known as “Kountry Wayne,” is not your average standup comedian. If you asked him to describe himself, he would say he is just a reserved vegan and father of eight who wants what’s best for his kids. Hailing from Millen, Georgia, Wayne grew up with aspirations of becoming a super-star rapper, however those ambitions quickly changed when he posted a video to Facebook and became a viral sensation overnight. Wayne attacked his new found fame head on and grew his audience to over 4 Million followers across Facebook &amp; Instagram by delivering amazing content on a daily basis. Never willing to say no to a fan, Wayne heeded their calls when asked to perform standup comedy. He initially started performing in small clubs in Atlanta and by 2016 had embarked on a 45 city sold out tour (2016 Child Support Tour). Since then Wayne has consistently performed year-round, regularly selling out clubs &amp; theaters across the country to a diverse, wide-reaching audience with his unique brand of high energy, faith based, and clean content. Wayne still resides in South Georgia where he runs two successful business in addition to his presence online and on the road. With his humble roots and unbridled energy it’s clear Wayne will be making people laugh for years to come.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/07/89/50/11/Original.jpg?v=3?v=3" alt="Kountry Wayne"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Wallace (Feb 13-15)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/george+wallace/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/george+wallace/</guid>
      <description>Feb 13-15 - By the age of six, George Wallace knew he wanted to be a comedian. He always enjoyed making people laugh, but he also knew the importance of an education. He attended the University of Akron, Ohio and upon graduating with degrees in Transportation, Marketing/Advertising, plus advance studies in Radio and Television from Columbia School of Broadcasting. Literally, a rags-to-riches story, Wallace went from selling rags to VP of Advertising. Still, his dream of being a comedian had a strong hold on him. Within a week of leaving the advertising field, he began to perform stand-up comedy and was offered a job writing for “The Redd Foxx Show.” Wallace is currently pursuing dual coursework at University of Phoenix and DeVry. With his writing and stand-up experience, Wallace began landing television appearances. Wallace was awarded a Lifetime Achievement Award at the 2013 Soul Train/Centric Comedy All-Star Awards; and won Best Stand Up Comedian at the prestigious American Comedy Awards after four consecutive nominations. As a veteran radio personality, he has also made appearances on “The Steve Harvey Morning Show” and is a charter member of “The Tom Joyner Morning Show.” In 2004 Wallace appeared as the headlining star of his own show at The Flamingo Hotel in Las Vegas for a 30 day run. Sin City showed its admiration by extending Wallace’s contract indefinitely and nicknaming him “The New Mr. Vegas.” Unlike any other comedy show in Las Vegas, Wallace gave away a number of prizes every night including CDs, DVDs, diamond necklaces, dinner at prestigious restaurants, gourmet chocolates, tropical cruises and even a new car. He celebrated his 10th Anniversary headlining at the Flamingo in March 2014, announced he was closing the show to head back out on the road. Wallace regularly performs in comedy clubs across the country and is an ambassador for the United States government, performing at military bases all over the world. His first book, LAFF IT OFF (Chaite Press) was published in 2014. A tome of life wisdom, humor and insight from a lifetime of observation, the book is in its third printing. www.georgewallace.net Wallace’s most recognized material is his “I Be Thinkin’” lines and jokes about everything from conversational thoughts to political aspirations. Each show he engages members of the audience in comical banter. If provoked, he might even throw out a few of his signature “Yo Mama” jokes. He shows his gratitude to the audience by signing autographs and taking photos after every show. Audience members never know what will happen at the George Wallace show. Wallace is an evolving comedian, which is why his show is different every night. He’s always thinkin’. Fans can now get a taste of what Wallace be thinkin’ on Twitter @MrGeorgeWallace&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/08/91/56/31/Original.jpg?v=1" alt="George Wallace"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zainab Johnson (Feb 6-7)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/zainab+johnson/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/zainab+johnson/</guid>
      <description>Feb 6-7 - Zainab Johnson is a stand-up comedian, actress, and writer. Zainab’s comedy is based on her unique point-of-view, which was shaped growing up in Harlem as one of thirteen siblings in a black Muslim family. After getting a degree in Education and Math and taking a job as a teacher, she quickly learned that she had a different calling. Zainab is currently a series regular on the Amazon Original hit series titled UPLOAD from Greg Daniels, she is one of the hosts for Netflix's show 100 HUMANS, and starred as Dr. Hanniel in the brilliantly written web series AVANT-GUARDIANS. She made her first late night stand up appearance on NBC's LATE NIGHT WITH SETH MEYERS, and had breakout appearances on HBO’s ALL DEF COMEDY, NBC’s LAST COMIC STANDING, and has performed at the JFL Comedy Festival in Montreal first as a "New Face of Comedy", then as one of "Variety's Top 10 Comics to Watch", and most recently on the longest running JFL show "Just For The Culture". She is a paid regular at The Comedy Store, The Improv, and Laugh Factory in Los Angeles as well as the Comedy Cellar in New York City. Her first hourlong special, Hijabs Off, is now available to stream on Amazon.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/08/57/25/11/Original.jpg?v=4?v=4" alt="Zainab Johnson"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiona Cauley (Feb 5)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/fiona+cauley/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/fiona+cauley/</guid>
      <description>Feb 5 - Fiona Cauley uses her quick wit and dark sense of humor to give some insight into what life is like as a disabled female comic. Based out of Nashville, TN, she is a regular at Zanies Comedy Club and any local hotdog stand. She can also be found in Austin, TX dropping into the world famous Comedy Mothership and as a special guest on Kill Tony. Be sure to catch her rolling through a town near you!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/09/71/29/13/Original.jpg?v=2?v=2" alt="Fiona Cauley"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Plumb (Jan 29)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/brian+plumb/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/brian+plumb/</guid>
      <description>Jan 29 - Brian’s storytelling and engaging style has made him a favorite across the country. He has shared the stage with Nate Bargatze, Brad Williams, Big Jay Oakerson, and many more. When he is not touring with T.J Miller, he can be seen around the New England area.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/09/68/00/74/Original.jpg?v=2?v=2" alt="Brian Plumb"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rene Vaca (Jan 24-25)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/rene+vaca/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/rene+vaca/</guid>
      <description>Jan 24-25 - Standup NBC winner Rene Vaca was born and raised in the San Fernando Valley in southern California. After his father was incarcerated, he started his own landscaping business at the age of 15. That came to an end when he was accepted to the University of California, Merced. Vaca has since been pursuing his dream in stand-up comedy and recently just won the 16th annual StandUp NBC competition! He has shared the stage with revered industry comedians such as Bill Burr, Ken Jeong, Amir K., Jamie Kennedy and much more!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/08/03/74/61/Original.jpg?v=4?v=5" alt="Rene Vaca"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Salem (Dec 26)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/sam+salem/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/sam+salem/</guid>
      <description>Dec 26 - Once a midwesterner, Sam Salem is an LA-based comedian known best for fitting in with the youth (read: making up Gen Z slang for his students). When Sam isn’t headlining at clubs and theaters throughout the U.S., he’s creating online videos featuring his uniquely laidback comedic voice, reaching more than 100 million views across platforms. As a result, his comedy has been featured on EllenTV, iHeartRadio, and in national commentary on SportsCenter. Perhaps his most impressive feat, Sam faces his toughest audience when he’s not on stage: high school classrooms.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/08/74/92/61/Original.jpg?v=1?v=2" alt="Sam Salem"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNB Brunch (Jan 11)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/rnb+brunch/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/rnb+brunch/</guid>
      <description>Jan 11 - The RNB Brunch is a combination of good food, strong drinks, and great music! But it’s also an emotional roller coaster. A travel back in time. A fashion show, a photo shoot. It’s a day party, a family reunion, a dinner party, and a kick back. It’s a concert, church and karaoke. We take you through each decade of R&amp;B classics. We relive some of the best R&amp;B movie soundtracks and do every line dance you can think of. We have the most exciting RNB Trivia set built into our show. It’s like no other selling our shows in every city we go. Limited seating capacity available. Grab tickets as soon as possible.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/09/94/53/33/Original.jpg?v=4?v=4" alt="RNB Brunch"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Felipe Esparza: At My Leisure World Tour (Jun 5-6)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/felipe+esparza%3a+at+my+leisure+world+tour/14647033/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/felipe+esparza%3a+at+my+leisure+world+tour/14647033/</guid>
      <description>Jun 5-6 - Felipe Esparza is not just your average comedian - he's a force of nature on stage, leaving audiences in stitches with his wild stories and real world experiences that make up his material. Since winning NBC’s “Last Comic Standing” in 2010, Felipe has worked hard to solidify his place among the top touring headliners working today. With four successful stand-up specials under his belt at HBO and Netflix and his popular "What’s Up Fool? Podcast”, holding steady as a top comedy podcast for the last ten years, fans have gotten to know Felipe and the world he comes from, and they want more. They are flocking to his live shows to be part of the total experience. With Felipe’s new “At My Leisure” Tour launching fall of 2024, he’ll be going international for the first time, to include Australia, New Zealand, Canada and several European dates to close out the year. Felipe's infectious energy and undeniable charm make every live performance an unforgettable experience. In addition to his stand-up success, Felipe has started to make a name for himself on the small and big screens. With recurring roles on hit TV shows such as “Superstore”, “The Eric Andre Show”, “Gentefied”, and “Victor and Valentino”, as well as appearances in films including “Guest House” with Pauly Shore, “7th &amp; Union” with Omar Chaparro, “Daddy Daughter Trip” with Rob Schneider, and “You People” with Eddie Murphy and Jonah Hill, Felipe has proven himself to be a versatile and talented performer. Felipe will be working on his 5th stand-up special during this new tour, promising even more laughs and unforgettable moments. With a slew of exciting projects on the horizon, Felipe shows no signs of slowing down.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/13/27/06/03_Original.jpg?v=18" alt="Felipe Esparza: At My Leisure World Tour"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Eaton (Dec 31)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/eric+eaton/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/eric+eaton/</guid>
      <description>Dec 31 - Eric has performed all over the United States and can be seen on the hit TV Show Masters of Illusion. Eric has won a Merlin Award (Oscar’s of Magic) for Outstanding Comedy and Magic. Eric has had the opportunity amaze celebrities such as; George Lopez, Lou Ferrigno, Russell Peters, Desiigner, and many more in which you can find on his social media platforms; @themagicofericeaton. Eric puts on a great show that earns him high praise with his unique blend of magic, charm and comedic wit. People referred to his amazing comedic tendencies and his ability with magic to being the perfect combination for a compelling and entertaining show. All of Eric’s tricks include audience members. From the show’s start to the incredible finish, audience members find themselves on stage trading barbs with Eric and having the time of their lives! The interchange is classic entertainment at its best. Be prepared to sit back and laugh at the hilarious and incredible Comedy and Magic of Eric Eaton!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/09/76/26/88/Original.jpg?v=1" alt="Eric Eaton"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don McMillan 2.0 *Now Powered By AI (Jan 22)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/don+mcmillan+2.0+%2anow+powered+by+ai/14611103/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/don+mcmillan+2.0+%2anow+powered+by+ai/14611103/</guid>
      <description>Jan 22 - What do you get when you cross an Engineer with a stand-up comedian? You get Don McMillan. This former chip designer has been doing his one-of-a-kind, PowerPoint-Driven comedy show for audiences for over 20 years! In his show packed with graphs &amp; charts, Don will show you the funny side of your world that has been sitting right in front of you - you are just too busy working to notice. Don graduated from Stanford University with a Master's Degree in Electrical Engineering. He then went to work at AT&amp;T Bell Labs where he was part of the team that designed the world’s first 32-bit microprocessor. He then moved to Silicon Valley where he helped launch the start-up company, VLSI Technology. Then after 15 years in the tech world, Don quit his job to become a stand-up comedian. That year he won $100,000 as the Comedy Grand Champion on "Star Search". Don's been seen on "The Tonight Show", "HBO", and the "Comedy Central". These days, Don spends most of his time writing and performing customized corporate comedy shows for companies like Google, Apple, Amazon, Microsoft, Ford Motors, and Exxon/Mobil! Don has performed more than 800 corporate shows in the last 20 years and he was named the #1 Corporate Comedian by the CBS Business Network. Currently, you can check out his YouTube Channel at “YouTube.com/DonMcmillanComedy".&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/13/23/33/73_Original.jpg?v=4" alt="Don McMillan 2.0 *Now Powered By AI"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gerry Dee (Feb 26)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/gerry+dee/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/gerry+dee/</guid>
      <description>Feb 26 - Star of “Mr.D” on Amazon Prime and plays the role of “Templeton” on the FOX/Hulu series “Animal Control” alongside Joel McHale. He is a guest star in the new CBS comedy, “DMV”. Gerry Dee has been making audiences laugh for over two decades including a successful run on Season 5 of NBC’s “Last Comic Standing”. His new stand-up, special, “The Blink of An Eye” is set to land on Netflix this year! Dee, who was a private school teacher for nine years before giving it up for comedy. He has written two best selling books about teaching and parenting and is the current host of “Family Feud Canada” which just completed at seven season.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/10/05/34/33/Original.jpg?v=2?v=2" alt="Gerry Dee"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adam Ray (Mar 11-12)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/adam+ray/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/adam+ray/</guid>
      <description>Mar 11-12 - Adam Ray is a seasoned comedian and actor hailing from Seattle, renowned for his versatile performances across television, film, and digital platforms. His extensive acting credits include roles in critically acclaimed shows and movies such as Curb Your Enthusiasm, The Barbie Movie, MadTV, Hacks, Pam &amp; Tommy, and The Heat, among many others. In addition to his prolific work in traditional media, Adam has made significant strides in the digital space and live performances. He has a combined 2.7M+ followers across social media and his appearances on popular podcasts like Kill Tony, Bad Friends, and Two Bears, One Cave have garnered millions of views, with some episodes ranking among the most watched in the shows' histories. Adam is also the host of his own podcast, About Last Night Podcast, which features the comedian and actor interviewing some of the biggest celebrities in comedy, sports, and entertainment. Adam's talent for impressions and character work shines through his portrayals of iconic figures like Joe Biden, Dr. Phil, and original characters such as Bruce Robbins, Elaine, Jeremy, and Tony Caruso. These performances have not only captivated audiences but also contributed to the rapid growth of his YouTube and social channels, where his content continues to reach an ever-expanding audience. One of Adam's standout achievements was his July 16th, 2024, performance on Kill Tony episode #672, which not only captivated viewers but also shattered records, amassing over 15 million views within the first week. On the episode Adam Ray appears as Joe Biden and Shane Gillis appears as Donald Trump. This episode has since become the most popular in the show's history. Following the episode release, Adam Ray was inducted into the Kill Tony Hall of Fame live at Madison Square Garden. He was the first non-regular in the Kill Tony Hall of Fame. This achievement is a follow up to Adam Ray being awarded as the 2023 Kill Tony Guest of the Year. Riding the wave of his success, Adam took his show, Dr. Phil LIVE! on the road with a national theater tour including 50 different shows. The tour offered fans an electrifying mix of stand-up, crowd interactions, celebrity guests, surprise characters, and unforgettable moments. The final Dr. Phil LIVE! show will occur in Los Angeles at The Wiltern on December 16, 2025. Adam Ray brought his Dr. Phil parody to Netflix on November 19, 2024, with the release of Adam Ray is Dr. Phil UNLEASHED. The special features comedian Adam Ray coming face to face with Dr. Phil himself. His recent stand-up comedy special, Like and Subscribe, has received over a million views and further solidified his status as a must-watch performer. As Adam continues to tour across the country and internationally, he remains one of the most dynamic and entertaining figures in comedy today, consistently delivering performances that leave audiences eagerly anticipating what's next. In 2026, Adam kicks off the WHO IS ME Tour, performing stand-up comedy in theaters across North America. For additional dates and info, go to: adamraycomedy.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/08/71/08/71/Original.jpg?v=5?v=6" alt="Adam Ray"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mix &amp; Mingle Tour 2025 starring Sheryl Underwood, Kyle Erby &amp; Mike Washington (Mar 20-21)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/the+mix+%26+mingle+tour+2025+starring+sheryl+underwood%2c+kyle+erby+%26+mike+washington/14353523/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/the+mix+%26+mingle+tour+2025+starring+sheryl+underwood%2c+kyle+erby+%26+mike+washington/14353523/</guid>
      <description>Mar 20-21 - Owner and CEO - Pack Rat Productions Inc. Entertainer Entrepreneur Philanthropist &amp; 23rd International President of Zeta Phi Beta Sorority Inc. Sheryl Underwood is a savvy businesswoman philanthropist and a multi-faceted multi-media entrepreneur who is recognized as one of the most articulate well-informed women of our time. She is a much sought after entertainer and public speaker who is described as one of the world’s brightest contemporary humorists. Underwood is Owner and Chief Executive Officer of Pack Rat Productions Inc. and is the 23rd International President of Zeta Phi Beta Sorority Inc. the only full-time entertainer to ever hold the sorority’s highest post. Underwood joined the television show THE TALK on CBS for the start of season two sitting alongside hosts Julie Chen Sara Gilbert Sharon Osbourne and Aisha Tyler. The show averages over 2 million viewers per day. With Underwood at the table THE TALK received its first Daytime Emmy nomination and a 5th year renewal on CBS television. Underwood who has received numerous awards and accolades was named one of the 10 most influential talk show hosts on Twitter in 2012. Underwood has appeared on multiple episodes of the Emmy winning CBS daytime drama The Young and the Restless and has starred in such films as Bullworth (starring Warren Beatty) I Got the Hook Up and Beauty Shop (starring Queen Latifah). In addition, Underwood was the host of Black Entertainment Television’s (BET’s) Comic View and Holla a talk show she created and produced which was loosely based on Bill Maher’s Politically Incorrect. She is a weekly contributor on the Steve Harvey Morning Show also serving as “guest host” and appears on The Steve Harvey Project the television version of the show airing on BET Centric. Underwood also hosted The Sheryl Underwood Show on Jamie Foxx’s The Foxxhole airing on Sirius 106/XM 149 where she provided a mix of political satire comedy and music. She can be heard on the radio daily from 3--?7 pm on “Sheryl Underwood Radio” airing on The Juice 107.3 (WJUC) in Toledo Ohio and North Carolina A&amp;T State University’s WNAA 90.1 FM. Underwood was the host of Martin Lawrence Presents 1st Amendment Stand-Up and is a former contributor to the Tom Joyner Morning Show. Underwood has appeared on the Dr. Phil Show FOX television network morning show Fox and Friends the Joy Behar Show WPIX in New York City The View created by ABC News Correspondent Barbara Walters OMG! Insider and CBS This Morning.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/12/99/78/63_Original.jpg?v=6" alt="The Mix &amp; Mingle Tour 2025 starring Sheryl Underwood, Kyle Erby &amp; Mike Washington"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UMPIRE UNMASKED! A Comedy Show with Vincent Chapman (Apr 9)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/umpire+unmasked%21+a+comedy+show+with+vincent+chapman/14004544/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/umpire+unmasked%21+a+comedy+show+with+vincent+chapman/14004544/</guid>
      <description>Apr 9 - UMPIRE UNMASKED throws out the same old boring comedy shows and brings the heat with a lineup of standup heavy hitters who aren’t afraid to swing for the fences. This high-energy showcase brings together some of the funniest performers in the game for a night of big hits, hot takes, and comedic chaos that will keep the crowd roaring long after the final pitch. Hosted by Vincent Chapman “the Dancing Ump”, UMPIRE UNMASKED, features comedians turning life’s curveballs into punchlines and knocking every set out of the park. Whether you’re a die-hard baseball fan or just here for a good time, this show guarantees premium laughs, good vibes and the kind of late-night excitement that is sure to leave you in stitches. Come take your seat – you’re about to witness comedy with full authority!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/12/75/46/44_Original.jpg?v=4" alt="UMPIRE UNMASKED! A Comedy Show with Vincent Chapman"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jason Cheny (Mar 27-29)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/jason+cheny/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/jason+cheny/</guid>
      <description>Mar 27-29 - Jason Cheny is a Taiwanese American standup comedian based in Los Angeles. Jason has toured all over Asia including Singapore, Hong Kong, Taiwan, and in comedy clubs all across the US. Jason can be seen on LAUGHS for Fox/Hulu and you can stream his comedy album Growing Painson Spotify and iTunes. Catch him on tour in a city near you!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/08/81/65/51/Original.jpg?v=2?v=2" alt="Jason Cheny"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doughboys Podcast (May 27)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/doughboys+podcast/13990884/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/doughboys+podcast/13990884/</guid>
      <description>May 27 - Doughboys is the iHeartRadio award-winning Best Food Podcast featured on Good Morning America and The Simpsons. Hosts and longtime frenemies Mike Mitchell and Nick Wiger review chain restaurants and bicker about absolutely everything. Past guests include Chris Pratt, Sarah Silverman, and Nicole Byer. Mike Mitchell is an actor, comedian, and cat dad of Wolly and Irma originally from Quincy, Massachusetts, the birthplace of Dunkin’ Donuts. His credits include Brooklyn Nine-Nine, The Tomorrow War, and Twisted Metal. Nick Wiger (rhymes with "tiger") is a writer, director, and game designer originally from Lakewood, California, the birthplace of Denny’s. He also co hosts the video game podcast Get Played.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/12/74/26/54_Original.jpg?v=3" alt="Doughboys Podcast"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Heffron (Jan 8-10)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/john+heffron/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/john+heffron/</guid>
      <description>Jan 8-10 - Energetic and accessible, acclaimed standup John Heffron shares an array of relatable experiences from childhood through life as a married father. He’s learned a thing or two about relationships with family, friends, and even himself along his journeys, gaining an astute, uniquely honest perspective widely praised among his comedy peers. Audiences of all ages relate to his enthusiastic, hard-won wisdom, recognizing how often the path to maturity is marked by universal triumphs and failures. Rather than mock differences, the Detroit native aims to engage, connect, and enlighten. Long before emerging victorious in the second season of NBC’s hit reality competition Last Comic Standing, Heffron first took the stage at the University of Michigan campus’s Main Street Comedy Showcase. He soon found himself skipping night classes to pursue his passion and branching into FM radio, serving as Danny Bonaduce’s wingman on Detroit’s Number One morning show, Danny Bonaduce and the Q Crew. Along with appearances on The Tonight Show , Chelsea Lately, The Late Late Show, HBO, FX, VH1, A&amp;E, and CMT, Heffron remains one of a small handful of veteran performers to tape two separate Comedy Central specials and has An Hour Special “Middle Class Funny” on Netflix. In the podcasting realm, Heffron has guested on WTF with Marc Maron, The Joe Rogan Experience, and Ari Shaffir’s Skeptic Tank. He launched his own The State I’m In on the All Things Comedy network in August 2014. Much like his self-effacing live material, Heffron’s podcast invites guests and listeners alike to explore the ever-fluctuating position they find themselves in both physically and mentally. In addition to headlining clubs and appearing at festivals around the world, Heffron remains in high demand as a performer at events for numerous Fortune 50 companies including Mercedes, Frito Lay, Sonic, Johnson &amp; Johnson, Ernst and Young, And The FBI Just to name a few. His four albums, Middle Class Funny DVD, and best-selling advice book I Come to You From the Future: Everything You’ll Need to Know Before You Know It are available on iTunes and Amazon.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/09/49/91/34/Original.jpg?v=1" alt="John Heffron"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Franjola (Mar 5)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/chris+franjola/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/chris+franjola/</guid>
      <description>Mar 5 - Chris Franjola is a writer/comedian who can currently be heard hosting his highly successful podcast, Cover To Cover With Chris Franjola (over 1500 5 star iTunes reviews &amp; Top 50 iTunes Comedy podcasts) also he’s a frequent contributor on Heather McDonald’s wildly successful podcast, Juicy Scoop. Chris can currently be seen as a regular panel guest on Lights Out with David Spade on Comedy Central &amp; Fox’s hit gameshow, Punchline. Chris was also a writer and a regular performer on E!’s hit show “Chelsea Lately" for 8 years. Together with the talented writing staff, Chris wrote over 1500 episodes while performing on the show more than anyone else beside Chelsea Handler and Chuy. During his time on the show Chris created some of the shows most memorable characters like Gay Caveman, Bieber Man, Johnny Depp, Seventeen Magazine Players and many more. He also starred on the critically acclaimed scripted comedy series “After Lately,” which aired for three seasons on E!, he was the host of the Sons of Anarchy aftershow Anarchy Afterword, airing live on FX. Last year Chris released his first comedy album "The Shallow End" which received rave reviews and stayed in iTunes Top 10 Comedy Albums for 5 weeks. Earlier this year Chris could be seen as a contributing panelist on The Josh Wolf Show on CMT and Funniest Fails on Fox. When he isn’t busy writing and acting, he’s performing stand-up on the road, headlining venues all over the country. Before Chelsea Lately, Chris wrote for other shows, including Family Guy, the MTV Video Music Awards, and the original Chelsea Handler Show.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/07/75/72/51/Original.jpg?v=4?v=5" alt="Chris Franjola"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mojo Brookzz: I Know You F*ckin Lying Tour (Jan 15-18)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/mojo+brookzz%3a+i+know+you+f%2ackin+lying+tour/13904914/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/event/mojo+brookzz%3a+i+know+you+f%2ackin+lying+tour/13904914/</guid>
      <description>Jan 15-18 - Dyon “Mojo” Brooks is an actor, writer, producer, and stand-up comedian. As a comic, Brooks is nationally acclaimed and celebrated having toured with legends such as Mike Epps, Martin Lawrence, and Deon Cole to name a few. He recently wrapped his headlining nationwide “Unhand Me Now” Tour which sold out every single with multiple added shows in nearly every location. This tour also marks Brooks’ transition from fully sold-out club weekends into headlining theatres with sold out stops at Atlanta’s Center Stage, Memphis’s Minglewood Hall, and two sold-out Sunday night shows at Chicago’s historic Vic theatre. Additionally, Dyon can be seen on the most recent Season [21] of Nick Cannon’s WILD N OUT, having been hand selected by Cannon who is a fan of Brooks viral sketch comedy videos that can be found across his social media pages, which have amassed millions of views and over 26.5 million likes. Brooks counts more than 1.1 million Instagram followers, 1.5 million Facebook followers, and over 1.3 million TikTok followers. A Chicago native, Brooks frequently collaborates with the Chicago Bears and contributed to a mid-west Emmy win for his writing efforts across commercial and digital work the team continues to do with him. Additionally, Brooks has lent his comedic acting talents to music videos including Lil Durk’s hit Sad Songs. When not entertaining audiences, Brooks gives back to his community in Chicago, dedicating his time and resources to support youth development programs, demonstrating his commitment to making a positive impact beyond the stage and screen. From February to May of 2025, Brooks will again join the multi-city WE THEM ONES arena tour – a package which he was a part of from its inception in 2024. The Mike Epps hosted tour features acts such as Karlous Miller, Tony Roberts, and Kountry Wayne with Brooks in a prominent position within the line up. Following the conclusion of WE THEM ONES, Brooks will set out on his fourth headlining tour with stops at multiple different theatres across the nation. Plans on screen for 2025 include going out with a few different original ideas across film and television while continuing to expand his reach with auditions across both comedy and drama.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/12/74/53/54_Original.jpg?v=1" alt="Mojo Brookzz: I Know You F*ckin Lying Tour"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carlos Mencia (Mar 13-15)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/carlos+mencia/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/carlos+mencia/</guid>
      <description>Mar 13-15 - Comedian Carlos Mencia is best known for his raw and unfiltered style of comedy, which he has showcased to great success on comedy stages, and in television shows and movies. He has recently gone back to his comedic roots on his No Hate No Fear comedy tour, sharing his newest material with smaller, more intimate audiences. As a comedian who finds the hilarious irony in both the day-to-day and the newsworthy events, Carlos is never lacking in material; he recently shot two stand-up specials due out later this year. Carlos will also reprise his role as Felix Boulevardez in Disney+'s "The Proud Family: Louder and Prouder," the revival of the groundbreaking animated series "The Proud Family." The show is heading into its second season. Mencia comes from a humble background, born in San Pedro Sula, Honduras, the 17th of 18 children. His parents sent him to the United States when he was three months old, where he was raised in the Maravilla Projects in Los Angeles by his aunt and uncle. In his early teens, Mencia moved back to Honduras. When Mencia returned to Los Angeles, he showed such educational prowess that he pursued a career in engineering. But an amateur night at the world-renowned Laugh Factory comedy club would change his path, and a career in comedy began. He became a regular at The Comedy Store, performing nightly. After he found success on the Los Angeles comedy circuit, Mencia was named International Comedy Grand Champion from Buscando Estrellas (the Latin version of Star Search), eventually landing on shows such as "In Living Color," "The Arsenio Hall Show," and "An Evening at the Improv." Mencia continued his journey up the comedy ladder by headlining stand-up tours and starring in stand-up TV specials. In 2002, he received a CableACE Award nomination for Best Stand-Up Comedy Special for his HBO special. Comedy Central soon took notice and the show "Mind of Mencia" went into development. Created by Carlos and comedy producer Robert Morton, the comedy series featured Carlos and his crew with their merciless mix of up-close stand-up, unconventional street interviews, and shocking commercial parodies. The show was an instant hit, and propelled Mencia to the comedy elite. After the first season, Comedy Central signed Mencia back for an original stand-up special, "Carlos Mencia: No Strings Attached," the first Comedy Central Stand-up Special DVD to achieve Platinum sales status. Throughout the four seasons of “Mind of Mencia,” Carlos never stopped performing live, headlining shows across the country and internationally. “Comedy is my art, and fans are my passion,” he has said. Always looking to give back to those fans, Mencia has entertained troops serving overseas for USO tours in Turkey, Kirkuk, Baghdad, Qatar, Afghanistan, and many other countries. Later, Mencia went on to star on the big screen. He starred opposite Ben Stiller and Michelle Monaghan in "The Heartbreak Kid," and in the family-comedy "Our Family Wedding," alongside America Ferrara and Forrest Whitaker. Carlos Mencia presently lives in Los Angeles with his wife and two sons.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/07/87/32/81/Original.jpg?v=3" alt="Carlos Mencia"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Des Bishop (Mar 26)</title>
      <link>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/des+bishop/</link>
      <guid>https://improv.com/raleigh/comic/des+bishop/</guid>
      <description>Mar 26 - Now a massive star in Ireland, native New Yorker, Des moved from Queens to Ireland in his mid teens in 1990. He first came to prominence with his extraordinary TV series The Des Bishop Work Experience (2004), where he lived on minimum wage in a series of different jobs in Ireland. Mixing this documentary footage with stand-up, the series became one of the most talked-about of the year, and propelled Des into national stardom. In 2006, he embarked on his second critically acclaimed TV series, Joy In The Hood, where he taught stand-up comedy in disadvantaged areas in four major Irish cities. Another hugely successful live tour followed including invitations to the Just For Laughs Festival in Montreal and the Melbourne Comedy Festival in Australia. Des’s most recent project took him to Beijing, China in 2013 to learn Mandarin and he has been living there for the past 18 months. He is now fluent and the show, Breaking China was another major hit for broadcaster RTE in 2014 and he also made a half hour radio documentary about the rise of Stand Up in China for the BBC World Service called “Stand up for China”. His live show again opened at the Edinburgh Festival where he played to over 5,000 people and included an invitation to perform at the Soho Theatre in London and a return to Barrow Street in New York.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.ticketweb.com/i/00/09/55/10/34/Original.jpg?v=3?v=3" alt="Des Bishop"/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
